[
    {
        "question" : "What's the name of the brand created by A$AP MOB?",
        "answer" : "VLONE"
    },

    {
        "question" : "Why did Young Thug wear a dress for his photoshoot?",
        "answer" : "To hide his gun"
    },
        {
        "question" : "Who created the brand Le Fleur?",
        "answer" : "Tyler The Creator"
    },
        {
        "question" : "What controversial accessory did Frank Ocean drop under his brand blonde?",
        "answer" : "a cock ring"
    },
        {
        "question" : "Who has the worst fits of all? I'm talking dressed up like a dyke auntie.",
        "answer" : "Gunna"
    },
        {
        "question" : "Is it possible to have too much swag?",
        "answer" : "No"
    },
        {
        "question" : "Is it possible to have too much sag?",
        "answer" : "No"
    },
        {
        "question" : "Who's the popular diamond seller in LA?",
        "answer" : "Elliot"
    },
        {
        "question" : "Does Playboi Carti have a stylist?",
        "answer" : "No"
    },
        {
        "question" : "What's most important? The brand or the drip?",
        "answer" : "the drip"
    }
    
]